

# **CURICULUM VITAE OBENG JEFFREY**

# **PERSONAL OBJECTIVE**

My goal as an IT Technician is to apply my indepth knowledge in hardware and software applications and develop IT solutions to maintain continuity and efficiency of work in the organization. Equipped with solid background in systems installation, IT repair and replacement, troubleshooting and patching, I am positive that this objective can be achieved. My two years' experience in two different companies has enhanced my skills and broadened my understanding in supporting various computer systems and networks. I am also very knowledgeable in using different windows server systems, Active Directories and know how to manipulate subnets and firewalls.

# **CONTACT**



stunite69@@gmail.com



+233-24-773-9288



Obuasi, Ashanti Region



https://jeffreyobeng.netlify.app/

## **HOBBIE**



Photography







### **EDUCATION**

### **Presbyterian University College**

Bachelor in Information Technology 2018-2021

### **NIIT University College**

Professional Diploma in Information Technology (Networking Engineering) September 2013 – February 2016

# **OTHER QUALIFICATIONS**

#### **UDEMY COURSES**

- ♦ Cisco CCNA 200-301
- ♦ After Effects CC 2020
- ❖ Automate the Boring Stuff with Python Programming
- ❖Cisco CCNA Packet Tracer Ultimate Lab 200-301
- CompTIA A+ Certification (220-1002)
- ♦ Kali Linux
- ❖Java: Build Desktop & Android Mobile Apps
- ❖Social engineering
- Linux Administration Bootcamp
- ❖The Complete 2021 Web development Bootcamp
- ❖The Complete JavaScript Course 2021
- ♦ Web Server IIS Mastery Course
- ❖Virtual Private Network (VPN)
- ❖Windows Server 2012 System Administration
- ❖Windows Server 2019

#### **COURSERA COURSES**

- Google IT Support
- Project Management
- Data Analytics
- IT Automation with Python
- Cybersecurity
- UX Design





# **SKILLS PROFILE**

- ❖In Depth knowledge of Windows, Mac and Linux Desktop systems, including installation, patching, troubleshooting and hardware replacement.
- ♦ Strong Knowledge of Active directory, group policy, Exchange 2010, SIMS, MS SQL 2008.
- ♦ Excellent working knowledge of Windows XP and Windows 7, Windows 2003/2008 Server, Terminal Services, Active Directory, IPSEC and SSL VPN, active directory, Exchange 2010 and VMware administration.
- ❖Strong ability to communicate technical information to non-technical Staff.
- Ability to conduct research into a wide range of computing issues.
- ♦ Ability to work as part of a team and communicate with staff at all levels

### **RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE**

IT Support Technician (Nabco Trainee)

Obuasi Municipal Assembly

November 2018 – August 2021

Supported and maintained the Company's IT systems including desktop provision, network infrastructure, and associated software and business applications.

Updates the register of IT assets and contributed to audits of IT licensing arrangements.

Coordinated IT equipment bookings and maintained equipment in a suitable condition for loan.

Advised staff and Members on their use of standard IT applications. Monitored system alerts and reports on servers and reported problems to the concerned IT Team Leader.

Updating OMA website.

Handled server shutdowns and restored service according to documented procedures.

### IT Support Technician

Obuasi Municipal Library – Obuasi August 2017 – September 2018

- Monitored new IT developments and
- $\ensuremath{\diamondsuit}$  Supported the various systems and software packages currently in use.
- Provided a capability to tailor and customise functions and

- Maintained all hardware, software, applications and interfaces.
- Contributed to the proper installation, maintenance and disposal of desktop computers and printers.

#### IT Technician / Trainer

National Service Obuasi Municipal Library – Obuasi September 2016 – August 2017

- Monitored new IT developments
- Supported the various systems and software packages currently in use.
- Provided a capability to tailor and customise functions and applications to improve work practices.
- Maintained all hardware, software, applications and interfaces.
- Contributed to the proper installation, maintenance and disposal of desktop computers and printers.
- Train students and other registered member at the library
- E-Learning Tutor and provide assistance to clients when needed.

### REFERENCES

#### **OMA-MIT**

Mr. Salifu Amidu, Assistant Programmer Obuasi Municipal Assembly Mobile: 0249163041

#### **OMA-Library**

Mr. Philip Asamoah, Director Obuasi Municipal Assembly 0209104663 / 0242689107

#### **EMMREG COMPUTER SOLUTION**

Manager Goaso – Ahafo Region 0244986782

